<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chad Lucas</title>
    <link>https://cjlucas85.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chad Lucas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 20:30:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cjlucas85.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Stub</title>
      <link>https://cjlucas85.github.io/projects/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 20:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjlucas85.github.io/projects/projects/</guid>
      <description>Project Stub, will be removed when projects are added.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python: Functional Short-circuit Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://cjlucas85.github.io/blog/python-functional-short-circuit-evaluation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjlucas85.github.io/blog/python-functional-short-circuit-evaluation/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I made an interesting connection between some of Python&amp;rsquo;s builtin functions and generators. A common pattern in a project appeared where I needed to handle an increasing number different things needed to be checked in a string with a possible variety of approaches to be made. This resulted in the following pattern:
def check1(x): return x &amp;gt; 10 def check2(x): return x &amp;gt; 20 def check3(x): return x &amp;gt; 30 # .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>https://cjlucas85.github.io/blog/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjlucas85.github.io/blog/first-post/</guid>
      <description> First post. Page will be deleted once more content comes.
Images Code #!/usr/bin/env python3 import sys import os print(sys.argv) print(os.path.getcwd())  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://cjlucas85.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjlucas85.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>With this theme, it is possible to add small sections that only contains one page like this. It will automatically appears in the header, at the end.
Along with Ford Prefect, Dent barely escapes the Earth&amp;rsquo;s destruction as it is demolished to make way for a hyperspace bypass. Arthur spends the next several years, still wearing his dressing gown, helplessly launched from crisis to crisis while trying to straighten out his lifestyle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>https://cjlucas85.github.io/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjlucas85.github.io/home/</guid>
      <description>This is the home page. It will display the blog section if there is one, and a text before.
Hey ! Welcome to the Cocoa Enhanced theme. Here are some articles :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://cjlucas85.github.io/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjlucas85.github.io/license/</guid>
      <description>You can use this page to put a license on the contents of your blog, like so:
 The MIT License (MIT)
Copyright &amp;copy; 2015 Nishanth Shanmughamnishanth.gerrard@gmail.com
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>