<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chad Lucas</title>
    <link>https://cjlucas85.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chad Lucas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cjlucas85.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop Making Shell Scripts</title>
      <link>https://cjlucas85.github.io/blog/stop-making-shell-scripts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjlucas85.github.io/blog/stop-making-shell-scripts/</guid>
      <description>Shell Scripts are terrible, and you need to stop creating them.
For years, I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered a fair amount of shell scripting being used on various projects. Often shell scripting finds its away in tasks related to build systems, automated testing, source code management and similar tasks. These are all areas which well trained Software Engineers with good intentions have deemed a suitable tool for the job. They&amp;rsquo;re wrong. Instead of making things more streamline, a shell script will make things more unpredictable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Console Project</title>
      <link>https://cjlucas85.github.io/projects/console-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2019 20:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjlucas85.github.io/projects/console-project/</guid>
      <description>This project is a work in progress.
Here are an unorganized list of potential improvements to the Linux terminal environment.
PRESENTATION It might be that there are two or three different applications that are being described here. If this is the case they need to be broken up and tackled one at a time.
Question: How will this be presented? As an application or as a &amp;ldquo;layer&amp;rdquo; for which a shell is running while the application is running?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python: Functional Short-circuit Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://cjlucas85.github.io/blog/python-functional-short-circuit-evaluation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjlucas85.github.io/blog/python-functional-short-circuit-evaluation/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I made an interesting connection between some of Python&amp;rsquo;s builtin functions and generators. A common pattern in a project appeared where I needed to handle an increasing number different things needed to be checked in a string with a possible variety of approaches to be made. This resulted in the following pattern:
def check1(x): return x &amp;gt; 10 def check2(x): return x &amp;gt; 20 def check3(x): return x &amp;gt; 30 # .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://cjlucas85.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjlucas85.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>This page and the whole site is currently underdeveloped. I&amp;rsquo;m aiming to turn this in a place where I&amp;rsquo;ll post articles and projects related to programming, software engineering and similiar interests. In time, it will be filled with content. For now, enjoy what little I have to offer.
As is life, it&amp;rsquo;s a work in progress.
-cl</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>https://cjlucas85.github.io/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjlucas85.github.io/home/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://cjlucas85.github.io/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjlucas85.github.io/license/</guid>
      <description>Code examples on this blog is free to use under MIT; however, all else is subject to default copyright.
 The MIT License (MIT)
Copyright &amp;copy; 2019 Chad Lucas cjlucas85@gmail.com
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>